Guide to the Time Inc. Fortune Editorial Records 1951-2013 MS 3009-RG 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Personnel and Contributors Files, 1951-1977; 2.5 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
  - Mahoney, Stephen, 1961 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 21)
  - Main, Jerry, 1967 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 22)
  - Maurer, Herrymon, 1956-1958, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 23)
  - Mayer, Larry, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 24)
  - McDonald, John, 1951-1959 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 25)
  - McQuade, Walter, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 26)
  - Mecklin, John, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 27)
  - Meyer, Burt, 1962-1967 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 28)
  - Murphy, Charles J.V., 1953-1966, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 29-33)
  - Mydans, Carl and Shelley, 1969, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 34)
  - Norton-Taylor, Duncan, 1960-1965, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 35-36)
  - O'Hanlon, Thomas, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 37)
  - Parker, Sanford, 1965-1967, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 1)
  - Ratajczek, Dr. Donald, 1970, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 2)
  - Roosa, Robert, 1971, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 3-4)
  - Rostow, Eugene, 1966 (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 5)
  - Rostow, W.W., 1965 (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 6)
  - Siekman, Philip W. (Jr.), 1957-1973, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 7-9)
  - Silberman, Charles, 1953-1973, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 10-12)
  - Silberman, Charles [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R42)
  - Smith, Richard Austen, 1953-1956, 1964-1970, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 13)
  - Stryker, Perrin, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 14)
  - Stryker, Perrin [RESTRICTED], 1958-1959, undated (Offsite-box R42)
  - Thompson, Ed (Jr.), 1957, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 15)
  - Ways, Max, 1966-1967, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 16)
  - Whalen, Richard, 1964-1968, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 17-18)
  - Whyte, William H. (Jr.), 1952-1958, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 19)
  - Wierzynski, Gregory H., 1965-1967, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 20)
  - Wise, Tom, 1967-1968, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 21)
  - Yankelovich, Daniel, 1967-1973, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 22-23)
  - Yankelovich, Daniel [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R42)
  - Zalaznick, Sheldon, 1967-1969, undated (Offsite-box 2900, Folder 24)